Guide to the Livingston Family Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Curran and Mulford Family Papers, 1770-1966; Series XI; 11; (28 boxes) + 2 broadside folders
  - Henry H. Curran (1877–1966) papers
    - Photographs
      - Windmill, Amagansett, New York [photograph by Henry Curran], circa 1900 (Box 111, Folder 969)
    - Professional papers
      Arranged chronologically by office/position held
      Includes correspondence, documents, photographs, clippings, and writings
      - Congressional campaign, 1910 (Box 112, Folder 970)
      - Alderman and Chair of the Board of Aldermen, 1911-1917 (Box 112, Folder 971-977)
        Includes records for marriages performed, 1911-1916
      - City magistrate, 1917 (Box 112, Folder 978)
      - Manhattan borough president, 1919-1921 (Box 112, Folder 979-980)
      - Mayoral campaign, 1921 (Box 112, Folder 981-982)
      - Committee on Transit (New York County), 1923 (Box 112, Folder 983)
      - Commissioner for Immigration for the Port of New York
        - Files, 1923-1926 (Box 112, Folder 984-985)
        - Files, 1923-1926 (Box 113, Folder 986-989)
        - Immigration history clippings, 1851-1882
          Contains tearsheets from serials including Harper's and Leslie's weeklies, and competitors
      - City Club of New York, 1926-1928 (Box 113, Folder 990-991)
      - Association Against the Prohibition Amendment, 1928-1932 (Box 113, Folder 992-993)
      - National Economy League, 1932-1936 (Box 113, Folder 994)
      - Special Commissioner on Noise Abatement, 1935 (Box 113, Folder 995-996)
      - City of New York Arbitration Board, 1935 (Box 113, Folder 997)
      - City magistrate, 1936-1937 (Box 113, Folder 998-999)
      - Deputy mayor, 1937-1939 (Box 113, Folder 1000-1001)
        Recording (instantaneous disc, 12-inch, aluminum) of Henry Curran made by WNYC at the New York World's Fair, July 1, 1939, is in Restricted Fragile Papers, Box 161, folder 1280
      - City magistrate, 1939-1945 (Box 114, Folder 1002-1003)
      - Court of Special Sessions, 1945-1947 (Box 114, Folder 1004)
      - Retirement, 1947 (Box 114, Folder 1005-1006)
      - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1914-1927 (Box 114, Folder 1007)
      - Miscellaneous clippings, 1926-1965 (Box 114, Folder 1008)
    - Writings
      - Article in Forest and Stream, 1894 Oct 13
      - Columns from the New York Tribune, 1896, undated (Box 114, Folder 1009)
      - Essays for the Yale Review, 1913, 1915 (Box 114, Folder 1010)
        "Home Rule for American Cities" and "What the Ten-year Sergeant of Police Tells"
      - Writings on immigration, 1924-1926 (Box 114, Folder 1011-1012)
      - Pillar to Post, 1941 (Box 114, Folder 1013)
      - Pillar to Post, 1941-1950 (Box 115, Folder 1014-1015)
      - Writings from the New York Times Magazine, 1944-1945
      - "Topics of the Times" columns from the New York Times, 1947, 1951, undated (Box 115, Folder 1016-1017)
      - Writings from This Week magazine, 1944-1948
      - Columns from the Villager, 1950-1962
        Stored in: Oversize, Box 155, folders 1236-1239
      - "All Sorts and Conditions" [collected writings, unpublished], 1941-1960, undated (Box 115, Folder 1018-1019)
      - Autobiographical writings, 1947-1952
      - Miscellaneous writings, letters to editors, speeches, and research files, 1918-1957, undated (Box 115, Folder 1020-1032)
  - Mulford family papers
    - Coghill, Mary Mulford (1829-1898): family portrait photographs, 1867, undated (Box 116, Folder 1033)
    - Crosby, Elizabeth Mulford (1831-1879): portrait photographs, circa 1865-1875 (Box 116, Folder 1034)
    - Cunningham and Bliss genealogical notes, 1820, undated (Box 116, Folder 1035)
      Includes 19th-century wash drawing of Christ Church, Cambridge, Massachusetts
    - Cunningham family: portrait photographs and silhouettes, circa 1800, 1926, undated (Box 116, Folder 1036)
    - Mulford, Abram (1806-1882): portrait photograph, circa 1865 (Box 116, Folder 1037)
    - Mulford, B.: tickets to Yale College events, 1799, 1801 (Box 116, Folder 1038)
      An earlier ticket in Box 101, folder 873
    - Mulford genealogical material, with obituaries, 1880, 1930, undated (Box 116, Folder 1039)
    - Mulford, Hervey (1777-1847): photograph of portrait miniature, undated (Box 116, Folder 1040)
    - Mulford, James H. (1836-1885)
      - Account notebooks, 1871-1873 (Box 116, Folder 1041-1042)
      - Accounts with Charles W. Crosby, 1873-1874 (Box 116, Folder 1043)
      - Book of Common Prayer, undated (Box 116, Folder 1044)
      - "Composure in Prospect of Death", 1843 Jul (Box 117, Folder 1045)
        Meditation on the death George Mulford (1818-1843)
      - Parker, Joseph: correspondence, 1885, undated (Box 117, Folder 1046)
      - Partnership papers, 1847-1880 (Box 117, Folder 1047)
      - Portrait photographs, circa 1865-1885 (Box 117, Folder 1048-1050)
        See also: Box 117, folder 1061
      - Taber, Charles and Henry, portrait photographs, undated (Box 117, Folder 1051)
      - Trial balances sheets for firm, 1865-1867 (Box 117, Folder 1052)
      - United States Dept. of the Treasury, 1862-1863 (Box 117, Folder 1053)
        Concerns appointment as Auditor's Office clerk
      - Miscellaneous papers, 1817-1883, undated (Box 117, Folder 1054)
        Includes business cards with engraved plate
    - Mulford, James H., Jr. (1836-1885), 1861-1862 (Box 117, Folder 1055)
      Concerns his appointment as assistant paymaster, United States Navy, with two portrait photographs
    - Mulford, Mary Moore Cunningham Porter (1810-1897)
      - At-home cards, with plates engraved by Gimbrede, New York, 1849, undated (Box 117, Folder 1056)
      - Crosby, Elizabeth Atwater, undated (Box 117, Folder 1057)
      - Cunningham, Theodore Bliss and Winthrop, letters, 1872-1875 (Box 117, Folder 1058)
      - Curran, Eliza (Lilla) Mulford, letters, 1863 (Box 117, Folder 1059)
      - Personal papers, 1854, undated (Box 117, Folder 1060)
      - Portrait photographs, circa 1865-1880 (Box 117, Folder 1061)
    - New Haven relatives, miscellaneous: portrait photographs (unidentified), undated (Box 118, Folder 1062)
    - Parker family: portrait photographs, 1890, undated (Box 118, Folder 1063)
    - Robinson family: portrait photographs, undated (Box 118, Folder 1064)
    - Townsend family: portrait photographs, circa 1860-1865 (Box 118, Folder 1065)
    - Miscellaneous portrait photographs, identified, undated (Box 118, Folder 1066)
      Includes carte de visite portrait of Edwin and Edwina Booth by Mathew B. Brady
    - Miscellaneous portrait photographs and silhouettes, unidentified (Mulford and Curran?), 1852, undated (Box 118, Folder 1067-1068)
- Other Papers, 1702-1960; Series XII; 1; (3 boxes)
  John C. Livingston (1862–1956)
  John Callendar Livingston was the third of four sons of Herman T. Livingston (1827-1899) and Susan Rogers Livingston. Born on May 8, 1862, he married Louise Foote Bowler (1861-1933) in 1892, and the couple had one child, Louise Alida (1892-1967). Livingston died in New York on May 11, 1956.
  The series holds a random assortment of material which arrived with the papers and could not be attached to any of the series above. It includes folders of photographs of unidentified people and places; letters and documents of non-Oak Hill relations which ended up with the family, including some correspondence and a scrapbook compiled John C. Livingston; another scrapbook compiled by a cousin, Eliza Livingston (1812-1896), which was a gift to the family; a series of chromolithographs of the Mississippi Valley by Henry Lewis; and two letters unrelated to the family but signed by noted Americans. Also present are a folder of third-party letters written by various Livingston ancestors and relatives, most of which were likely acquired by gift or purchase by Oak Hill Livingstons, and a small collection of portraits (prints and photographs of paintings) of Livingston ancestors.
  Present at the end of the series is a set of papers relating to Robert C. Gillies, whose relationship to Oak Hill is unknown to Livingston family members who were contacted in 2010. Gillies appears to have been a graduate of Princeton University, served in the United States Army during World War I, and in 1939 was working for the Securities and Exchange Commission in Washington, D.C. The material is comprised of a folder of letters, approximately one hundred snapshot photographs, and a scrapbook. The latter holds newspaper clippings on general topics, along with two circular letters (1925-1926) from H.G.C. Hallock, a Princeton graduate (1893) who was serving as a missionary in Shanghai, China. The correspondence file holds letters to Gillies from his young son Bob, sent to him in New York and Washington from Princeton and summer camps. The photographs are mostly unlabeled but the few that are show the Princeton campus fire that destroyed Dickinson Hall and Marquand Chapel (May 15, 1920), the inauguration of President Warren G. Harding (March 4, 1921), a tennis match (undated), scenes and incidents from trips to Japan and Scotland (undated), and various unidentified people and landscapes.
  - Commemorative medal, with case, from the Art Treasures Exhibition, Manchester, England; T.R. & J. Pinches, medallist, 1857 (Box 119, Folder 1069)
  - Lewis, Henry: seven plates from Das Illustrirte Mississippithal (Dusseldorf: Arnz & Comp., [1854-1857]), chromolithographs (Box 119, Folder 1070)
  - Livingston, Eliza Helen (1812-1896), 1843, 1873-1915, undated (Box 119, Folder 1071-1072)
    Contains clippings and ephemera primarily about descendants of John Robert Livingston and Robert Montgomery Livingston; includes Freeborn Garrettson family; gift from Herbert Schultz to Henry H. Livingston, 1966
  - Livingston, John C. (1862-1956)
    - Correspondence and miscellaneous papers, 1918-1946 (Box 119, Folder 1073)
    - Portrait photograph of Louise Alida Livingston (1893-1967), taken in Nice, France, circa 1904 (Box 119, Folder 1074)
    - Scrapbook, 1877-1932 (Box 119, Folder 1075-1076)
      Contains clippings, obituaries, correspondence, manuscript notes, drawings, ephemera, and photographs related to Livingston family history, Robert Fulton, and Scotland; also contains correspondence regarding his gift of a baptistry for Trinity Church, New York, designed by architect Thomas Nash (1922)
  - Livingston letters, 1702-1824, 1903 (Box 120, Folder 1077)
    Contains letters from Robert Livingston(s) to Philip Livingston Jr. (1702), Pierre Van Cortlandt (1777), William Ludlow (1780), John Swift (1782), and Abraham Walton (1794), and a signed stock certificate for the North-River Steam-Boat Company (1821); from Philip Livingston to Volkert Oothout (1742); from William Livingston to Robert Livingston (19th-century copy of 1698 letter); from Asa Starkweather to Robert Le Roy Livingston (1824); and notes on the course of the Hudson River by Philip Livingston Jr. (undated). The Ludlow letter is accompanied by a note (1903) from Albany bookseller John Skinner to Anna Parker Pruyn, a Livingston family friend.
  - Livingston portraits, undated (Box 120, Folder 1078-1079)
    Includes images of Livingston ancestors and relations: Philip, Robert(s), John, Janet, Maria, and unidentified; most are reproductions of paintings and prints
  - McVitty, Honoria Livingston (1909-2000): wedding portrait and newspaper clipping, 1931
  - Miscellaneous drawings, undated (Box 120, Folder 1080)
    Contains two drawings by Harry W. Watrous and one by Harper Pennington
  - Miscellaneous letters, 1782, 1837 (Box 120, Folder 1081)
    Contains a letter from Benjamin Lincoln to George Clinton (1782), and a condolence letter from Andrew Jackson to an unidentified recipient (1837)
  - Miscellaneous prints, undated
  - Miscellaneous family papers, 1866-1960 (Box 120, Folder 1082-1083)
  - Political ephemera, 1904 (Box 120, Folder 1084)
    Contains delegate's badge to ticket to Republican National Convention, campaign button for Roosevelt/Fairbanks, and delegate's badge
  - Photographs: unidentified places and things, undated (Box 120, Folder 1085)
    Includes tintype of industrial site/factory/mill/mine
  - Photographs: unidentified people, undated (Box 120, Folder 1086)
  - Robert C. Gillies papers
    - Correspondence, 1934-1939 (Box 121, Folder 1087)
    - Photographs, 1920-1921, undated (Box 121, Folder 1088)
    - Scrapbook, 1922-1927 (Box 121, Folder 1089)
- OVERSIZE AND SPECIAL FORMATS, 8; (39 boxes)
  - From Series I. Early Papers
    - John Livingston papers: account/day book, 1792-1823 (Box 122)
    - Herman Livingston papers: ledger/day book, 1823-1834 (Box 122)
    - John Livingston papers: portraits (photographs and prints of portrait painting), undated (Box 123, Folder 1090)
    - John Livingston papers: will, 1810 (Box 123, Folder 1091)
    - John Livingston papers: New York Genesee Company of Adventurers, 1796 (Box 123, Folder 1092)
    - Herman and Sarah Livingston papers: portraits, undated (Box 123, Folder 1093)
    - Livingston family legal papers: deeds, leases, mortgages, indentures, etc., 1772-1835 (Box 123, Folder 1094-1099)
  - From Series II. Herman T. and Susan R. Livingston Papers
    - Illuminated Bible (New York: Harper & Brothers), with manuscript family record (1856-1967) between Old and New testaments, 1846 (Box 124)
    - Livingston, Edmund P.: photographs with horse and carriage at Oak Hill, circa 1880 (Box 125, Folder 1100)
    - Livingston, Edmund P.: scrapbook: clippings on Yale College athletics, 1876-1877 (Box 125, Folder 1101)
    - Livingston, Herman T.: newspaper pages with shipping advertisement, 1853 Mar 13 (Box 125, Folder 1102)
    - Livingston, Herman T. and Susan: portraits, undated (Box 125, Folder 1103)
    - Rogers, Anne Coleman: portrait photographs, 1896, undated (Box 125, Folder 1104)
  - From Series III. Herman and Emeline H. Livingston Papers
    - Antiques, 1936-1939 (Box 125, Folder 1105)
    - Bigelow, Poultney, 1912-1914 (Box 125, Folder 1106)
    - Livingston, Edmund P. (1889-1972) [son], 1918 (Box 125, Folder 1107)
    - Greene County Historical Society membership certificate, 1929 (Box 125, Folder 1108)
    - Miscellaneous documents, ephemera: article on Oak Hill and Leslie's Weekly, 1899, 1934 (Box 125, Folder 1109)
    - Lewis F. Payn Oil Company: oil derrick, circa 1910 (Box 125, Folder 1110)
    - Livingston, Herman and Emeline: portraits of children, circa 1900 (Box 125, Folder 1111)
    - Pruyn, J. V. L. and Anna Fenn: library of home at 13 Elk Street, Albany, NY, 1909 Nov (Box 125, Folder 1112)
    - Ships: Schooner Amorilla, 1925. undated (Box 125, Folder 1113)
    - Ships: Nielsen, August: Sloop Rascal, undated (Box 125, Folder 1114)
    - Ships: Rosenfeld, Morris: Schooner Teragram, undated (Box 126, Folder 1115)
    - Ships: Rudder "Nautotypes", circa 1903 (Box 126, Folder 1116)
    - Ships: Stebbins, N. L.: unidentified ships, undated (Box 126, Folder 1117)
    - Ships: miscellaneous photographs and prints, undated (Box 126, Folder 1118-1121)
    - Yale College Class of 1879: crew and reunion group portraits, 1879-1929 (Box 126, Folder 1122)
    - New-Bedford Daily Mercury, vol. 1, no. 137, 1831 Nov 8 (Box 126, Folder 1123)
    - Hopkins, Charles V.: diploma, St. Paul's School, 1887 (Box 126, Folder 1124)
    - Scrapbook: investment receipts and records (including Hopkins and Cornell estates), 1897-1935 (Box 127)
  - From Series IV. Anna P. Livingston Papers
    - Rice, Harriet Langdon: portrait photograph, circa 1900 (Box 128, Folder 1125)
    - Simpson, Clyde V.: photographs, undated (Box 128, Folder 1126)
    - Calendar, 1906 (Box 128, Folder 1127)
    - Colorado Mountain Club: Trail and Timberline, 1915-1916 (Box 128, Folder 1128)
    - Ephemera: article about sale of Jacksonville house, 1968 Apr 21 (Box 128, Folder 1129)
    - French print [view of Quimper], circa 1934 (Box 128, Folder 1130)
    - Japanese books (2), circa 1890 (Box 128, Folder 1131)
    - Japanese paintings (on silk and on paper), circa 1890 (Box 128, Folder 1132)
    - Japanese polychrome woodblock prints (14), circa 1890 (Box 128, Folder 1133)
    - World War I broadsides, 1918 (Box 128, Folder 1134)
    - Photograph album: Bermuda, Mexico, and Nassau, 1888-1897 (Box 129)
    - Photograph album: Colorado, California, Quebec, and South Carolina, 1897-1901 (Box 130)
    - Photograph album: Hawaii, the Philippines, and Japan, 1900 (Box 131)
    - Photograph album: American West and Southwest, 1905-1908 (Box 132)
    - Historic houses and buildings: Ludlow and Watson/Webb houses, Claverack, New York, circa 1900 (Box 133, Folder 1135)
    - Snapshots with friends, undated (Box 133, Folder 1136)
  - From Series V. Archibald R. Livingston Papers
    - Drawings: schematics of ship models, 1931 (Box 133, Folder 1137)
    - Drawings: miscellaneous sketches, 1884-1895 (Box 133, Folder 1138)
    - Leslie's Weekly, with feature on the Engineers corps and Puerto Rico, 1898 Oct 13 (Box 133, Folder 1139)
    - World War I: medallions and plaquettes, 1919, 1921, undated (Box 133, Folder 1140)
    - Scrapbook, 1881-1887 (Box 134)
    - Columbia University: group photographs, School of Mines, 1887, 1891 (Box 135, Folder 1141)
    - Ships, 1892, undated (Box 135, Folder 1142)
    - California and the American West: miscellaneous, undated (Box 135, Folder 1143)
    - New York State: Niagara Falls, circa 1895 (Box 135, Folder 1144)
    - Rhode Island: Newport, 1889-1890 (Box 135, Folder 1145)
    - Photograph album: Puerto Rico and Pennsylvania, 1892-1898 (Box 136)
    - Photograph album: New York and the American West, 1889-1910, undated (Box 137)
    - Photograph album: Colorado, Wyoming, Alaska, New York, and Canada, 1890-1897 (Box 138)
    - Photograph album: New Mexico, Mexico, and Colombia, 1891-1906 (Box 139)
    - Photograph album: American West, circa 1910 (Box 140)
  - From Series VI. Herman and Olga K. Livingston Papers
    - Columbia County Historical Society, 1940-1941 (Box 141, Folder 1146)
    - Diploma, St. Paul's School, 1898 (Box 141, Folder 1147)
    - Monogram transfer sets [for embroidery], circa 1920 (Box 141, Folder 1148)
    - Newspaper article about Oak Hill, 1952 Sep 28 (Box 141, Folder 1149)
    - Livingston, Alida Schuyler, circa 1920 (Box 141, Folder 1150)
    - St. Paul's School football team photograph, 1897 (Box 141, Folder 1151)
  - From Series VII. Henry H. and Mary Eleanor Livingston Papers
    - Rogers & Webb, 1922 (Box 142, Folder 1152)
    - Family correspondence, re: real estate: survey map of Oak Hill property, 1948 Mar 8 (Box 142, Folder 1153)
    - Miscellaneous ephemera and clippings, 1922, 1928 (Box 142, Folder 1154)
    - Photographs: Livingston children in military uniforms, circa 1941 (Box 142, Folder 1155)
    - Photographs: Henry H. Livingston, Taft School, circa 1904 (Box 142, Folder 1156)
    - Photographs: Henry H. Livingston, Yale University, 1906-1909 (Box 142, Folder 1157-1160)
    - Photographs: Henry H. Livingston, miscellaneous, undated (Box 142, Folder 1161)
    - Photographs: Mary Eleanor Curran Livingston, as child, circa 1889 (Box 142, Folder 1162)
    - Photographs: Mary Eleanor Curran Livingston, wedding photographs, 1916 (Box 142, Folder 1163)
    - Photographs: Mary Eleanor Curran Livingston, with grandchild, circa 1950 (Box 142, Folder 1164)
    - Photographs: Mary Eleanor Curran Livingston, friends, circa 1915 (Box 142, Folder 1165)
    - Photographs: Henry H. Livingston, Yale University, 1905-1947 (Box 143, Folder 1166)
  - From Series VIII. Henry H. and Maria B. Livingston Papers
    - Miscellaneous papers, 1986 (Box 143, Folder 1167)
    - Walter Miller's series on Livingstons in the Chatham Courier, 1957-1958, 1971 (Box 143, Folder 1168)
    - Miscellaneous clippings, 1943-1974 (Box 143, Folder 1169)
    - Hotchkiss School group portrait, circa 1936 (Box 144, Folder 1170)
    - Livingston family houses: Hermitage, 1983 (Box 144, Folder 1171)
    - Livingston family houses: Oak Hill, undated (Box 144, Folder 1172-1173)
    - Livingston family houses: miscellaneous, 1902 (Box 144, Folder 1174)
    - Livingstons in New York City, 1926, undated (Box 144, Folder 1175)
    - Olana [Frederic Church home]: aerial photographs (2), undated (Box 144, Folder 1176)
  - From Series IX. Oak Hill Iron Mining Company Records
    - Cash book, 1884-1889 (Box 145)
    - Day book, 1884-1889 (Box 146)
    - Journal, 1884-1889 (Box 147)
    - Ledger, with separate index, 1884-1889 (Box 148)
  - From Series XI. Curran and Mulford Family Papers
    - Holy Bible (New York: American Bible Society), with manuscript family record (1866-1905) between Old and New testaments, 1858 (Box 149)
    - Curran children: group portrait photograph, undated (Box 150, Folder 1177)
    - Curran, Henry Hastings: portrait engraving, undated (Box 150, Folder 1178)
    - Curran family home in Utica, New York, photograph, undated (Box 150, Folder 1179)
    - Curran family: miscellaneous papers, 1869-1945 (Box 150, Folder 1180)
    - Curran, John Elliott
      - New York State Bar admission certificates, 1873-1880 (Box 150, Folder 1181)
      - French prints, 1814-1830 (Box 150, Folder 1182-1184)
      - Italian drawings, undated (Box 150, Folder 1185)
      - Obituaries, 1890 (Box 150, Folder 1186)
      - Portrait photograph, undated (Box 150, Folder 1187)
      - Williston Seminary group portrait, circa 1865 (Box 150, Folder 1188)
      - Yale College campus photographs, circa 1869 (Box 150, Folder 1189)
      - Columns and essays, printed, 1887-1890 (Box 150, Folder 1190)
    - Curran, Eliza (Lilla) Phillips Mulford
      - Feather cloak material, 1936 (Box 151, Folder 1191)
      - Music instruction and recitals, 1897 Jun 12 (Box 151, Folder 1192)
      - Twing, A. T. (Alvin Tabor), 1876, undated (Box 151, Folder 1193)
      - Miscellaneous papers: clippings about Englewood, 1895 (Box 151, Folder 1194)
      - Photograph of Lilla and Henry Curran, circa 1877 (Box 151, Folder 1195)
      - Photographs of Queechy Lake, Canaan, New York, and Gideon S. Drowne home, circa 1890-1905 (Box 151, Folder 1196)
      - Obituaries, 1936 (Box 151, Folder 1197)
      - Writings: tearsheets and journal issues, 1874-1901 (Box 151, Folder 1198-1203)
    - Curran, Henry H.
      - Ephemera, 1945, undated (Box 151, Folder 1204)
      - Military service papers: World War I, 1916-1919 (Box 151, Folder 1205-1207)
      - Writings about Henry H. Curran, 1922-1950 (Box 151, Folder 1208)
      - Sheet music, 1901-1958 (Box 152, Folder 1209-1213)
      - Photographs, portraits, undated (Box 153, Folder 1214-1217)
      - Photographs, Yale University and alumni events, undated (Box 153, Folder 1218-1219)
      - Alderman and Chair of the Board of Aldermen, 1911-1917 (Box 154, Folder 1220)
      - Mayoral campaign, 1921 (Box 154, Folder 1221-1223)
      - Association Against the Prohibition Amendment, 1928-1932 (Box 154, Folder 1224)
      - Deputy mayor, 1937-1939 (Box 154, Folder 1225-1226)
      - City magistrate, 1943 (Box 154, Folder 1227)
      - Article in Forest and Stream, 1894 Oct 13 (Box 154, Folder 1228)
      - Writings on immigration, 1924-1926 (Box 154, Folder 1229-1230)
      - Pillar to Post, 1941 (Box 154, Folder 1231)
      - Articles from New York Times Magazine, 1944-1945 (Box 154, Folder 1232-1233)
      - Articles from This Week, 1944-1948 (Box 154, Folder 1234-1235)
      - Columns from the Villager, 1950-1962 (Box 155, Folder 1236-1239)
      - Autobiographical writings, 1947-1952 (Box 155, Folder 1240)
      - Miscellaneous writings, 1923-1950 (Box 155, Folder 1241-1242)
      - Military service papers: World War I, 1918 (Box 156, Folder 1243)
      - Yale University, 1898, undated (Box 156, Folder 1244)
      - Mayoral campaign, 1921 (Box 156, Folder 1245)
      - Association Against the Prohibition Amendment, 1928-1932 (Box 156, Folder 1246)